Peter Krysinski Software Engineer 381 J. St. Salt Lake City, UT 84103

Phone: 313.300.8118 Email: pakrysin@gmail.com GitHub: github.com/Pkrysinski/

LinkedIn: linkedin.com/in/peterkrysinski/

## **Professional Summary**

Web developer with a background in software engineering in various industries including enterprise level healthcare applications and automotive automation systems. Recently trained at the University of Utah coding bootcamp and earned a certificate in full-stack web development. Proven and demonstrable experience combining people skills with technical ability while building fast, efficient, and complex applications from conception to production with modern tech. Also loves all kinds of outdoor recreation, activities with friends, and eating his way around town.

## **Employment History**

Sr. Software Engineer

Centene Corporation

Detroit MI, Salt Lake City UT (remote 6 years)

July, 2014 - Present

Started as a junior developer working with the communications department helping program healthcare campaign software processes and patient EOB's. Was promoted to mid-level developer and advanced to the claims adjudication and payments team. Helped develop and improve numerous aspects of the claims processing tool, including 3rd party software integration with SFTP systems and API's. Now a senior engineer, helping build modernization platforms with modern tech to help convert legacy systems to modern architecture.

Controls Engineer

The Paslin Co.

Detroit, MI

March 2013 - July 2014

PLC programming and controls design for automated welding systems, HMI/Panel View configuration, troubleshooting and debugging of automation hardware and software. Customer-focused and teamwork driven projects for clients including Honda and Ford. International and domestic travel, up to 80%.

## Education

University of Utah
Certification, Full Stack Web Development Boot Camp
October 2022 - April 2023

## Syracuse University

Bachelor of Science, Information Management & Technology

September 2008 - December 2012

Skills	Tools & Paradigms
HTML CSS JavaScript Bootstrap Node.js Express.js React.js	Git API's Microsoft Office MVC MERN
SQL/NoSQL	